CURRICULUM – VITAE

Name : **RAJESH RANJAN**

Qualification: B.E. CIVIL ENGINEERING

Date of Birth : 01-07-1973

Sex : Male Marital status : Married Nationality : Indian

Mobile No. : 9589299347,9406037232 Email Id : ranjanrajesh39@gmail.com

KEY QUALIFICATION –

I am first class B.E. holder in civil engineering having approximately TWENTY ONE YEARS of experience in the field of highway Construction, Sewerage Supervision & Quality Control. The experience included the supervision, execution & Construction of Pipe line (150 to 1600mm Dia) Pavement layers of Highway. Quality control tests for different components of Flexible & rigid pavement as per the MORT&H specifications. Measurement of different items of road & CD work & its recording.

Also well conversant with carrying out various types of Survey for highway like establishing of horizontal & vertical control point. Carring out benchmark shifting. having also carried out topographical survey for different project sites. Well Conversant with MORT&H& IRC specifications & road work related codes.

EDUCATION –

B.E.in Civil Engineering from Bangalore University, Bangalore

(KARNATAKA)

Year of passing: Mar'1999

EMPLOYMENT RECORDS:

March' 2010 to Till Date

EMPLOYER : SIMPLEX INFRASTRUCTURES LTD.

Position : DEPUTY PROJECT MANAGER
Project : Sewerage Project Bilaspur City.
Client : Bilaspur Municipal Corporation.

Description:-

Responsible for conducting & performing of Pipe & Manhole Laying, Construction of Property Chamber and Property Connection, Restoration of Road (B.T & C.C). Ensure conformity of construction work as per the drawings, verify setting out data, ensure works as per IS/ MORT&H Specification.

Feb' 2006 to Feb 2010

EMPLOYER : ARTEFACT PROJECTS LTD.
Position : ASST. MATERIAL ENGINEER.

Project : Project management consultancy service for

P.M.G.S.Y. : (ADB). Korba (C.G.)

Description:-

Responsible for conducting & performing tests of highway material both in the laboratory and on the sites also analyzing and assuring this suitability and behaviour performance in the different layers of both Rigid & Flexible pavements. Ensure conformity of construction work as per the drawings, verify setting out data, preparation of BOQ& ensure works as per MORT&H Specification.

March 2005 to January 2006

EMPLOYER : Quest International Consultant

Position : Field Engineer

Project : Infrastructure & Town planning (IMC, Indore)

Description:-

Responsibilities included the supervision of work progress

Monitoring, preparation of monthly progress. Overall management of Construction activities.

Feb 2002 to Feb 2005

EMPLOYER : ACPL. Sherghati (Bihar)
Position : Asst. Highway Engineer.
Project : NH-2 (four lanning) NHAI,

Description:-

Approval of boorow area, Querry area. Stockpiles, Responsible for detail project Quality planning for highway project, calibration of lab & filed Equipment's Hot mix, batch mix plant sampling ,testing and also responsible for Monthly, Quartly progress report .ensure QA/QC the standard preparation of estimate of material used for construction & the estimate of costs. Preparation of bill & claims.

April 1999 to Jan 2002

EMPLOYER : TRIMURTI Construction Enterprizes

Position : Site Engineer.

Project : E.R.Road Project (Bihar)

Description:-

Construction embankment, subgrade, GSB, WBM, CC Road day to day planning & Checking of construction schedule site instruction, test records & Maintain project diary & Preparation of progress report.

JOB RESPOSIBILITY -

- * Pipe Laying, Precast Manhole fixing, Property Connection
- * E/W, GSB, WBM, WMM, DBM, BC, DLC, PQC Preparation.
- * Laboratory tests for soil, WBM, B.T. & C.C. Works.
- * Taking all measurement maintain the required level.
- * Checking of sub Contractor bills.
- * Quantity takes from drawing.
- * Reporting to immediate Boss about the current status of work.
- * Liaisons with clients for technical details.

Languages Known:-

	Speak	Read	Write
English	Good	Excellent	Excellent
Hindi	Excellent	Excellent	Excellent

Contact Address –

Qtr No 27 Phase-I, Geetanjali City Bahtarai Road, Sarkanda Bilaspur (Chhattisgarh) PIN-495006

111 423000

Mob:- 9589299347,9406037232

Permanant Address -

S/o shri. U.Singh

Rampur

Jamalpur. Munger (Bihar)

Pin Code:-811 214

* Certification: I the undersigned, here by certify that to the best of my knowledge and belief, these data correctly describe me, my Qualification and my experience.

Signature

(RAJESH RANJAN)